我可以...告诉你
I could...  share with you.
可惜有一道暂停你的职业资格的禁令
If it weren't for the restrictions of your suspension?
是  按照我的理解
Yes, which, as I understand it,
它只是禁止我讨论未来的策略
prevents me from talking about future strategy, but not...
而不是过去的  因为这算是提供信息
Past. That would be updating?
我有这么做的权利
Which is within my rights.
然而我们还是在这里窃窃私语
Yet, we seem to be in here whispering.
是在咨询
Consulting.
你有什么主意呢
What do you got?
把冰球带进这起官司来
Bring hockey into it.
带进我们的案子吗
Into our case?
没错  他们的辩护是根据修正性比较过失
Yes. Their defense is based on modified comparative negligence.
如果我们的当事人要承担事故的一半责任
If our client is responsible for 50% of his accident,
他输了  但是...
he loses, but...